ADOLPH GASPER MAPUNDA

MikocheniA, Dares salaam, Tanzania | 255692536972 | adolphgasper@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/adomigold

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/adolph-gasper-

106474178/

Professional Summary

Well qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of back-end and front-end development requirements. Handle any part of the process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 3+ years of related experience.

Work History

Full stack software developer contractor Jan 2024 - Dec 2024 Dawa Mkononi

Dares

salaam

- Developed the DMRX sales force application, available on the Play Store, to enhance the efficiency of the sales, delivery, and warehouse teams.
- Streamlined daily operations for multiple teams, leading to improved coordination and productivity across the company.
- Designed and implemented backend systems that ensured the application was scalable and robust enough to handle the company's growing needs.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to gather requirements, troubleshoot issues, and deliver a user-friendly and reliable product.
- Provided ongoing support and updates to the DMRX application, ensuring it met evolving business needs and user feedback.

Full stack software developer

May 2023 - Jan 2024 Dares salaam

NBC via Ellipsis

- Developed high quality software inline with the customer established requirements.
- Used static code analysis to analyze code for consistency and test coverage.
- Drove continuous improvement by maintaining a working knowledge of the latest changes in software development, data and automation.
- Tracked issues and implemented changes to enforce adherence to test strategy for functional and non-functional requirements.
- Built reusable code and libraries to support future projects and optimize workflows.
- Reduce bugs and performance issues with improved testing architecture.
- Decreased system failures with diligent execution of unit and load testing.
- Provide input and technical content for customer-facing documentation, user help materials and customer training.

Shule Direct Dares salaam

 Identified areas for improvements in existing software programs and developed modifications.

- Coded per development, performance and secure coding standards.
- Developed Django base frameworks for complex data processing and micro- services.
- Performed root cause analysis and worked with manager and team members to resolve problems.
- Created cloud native software systems using advanced programming techniques.
- Colaborated with front-end developers and web designers to match visual design intent.
- Handled ongoing site iterations troubleshooting and maintenance post launching.

Full stack software developer

Nov 2020 - Dec 2021

OSIM Dares salaam

- Provide input and technical content for customer-facing documentation, user help materials and customer training.
- Oversaw the agile team in executing the full product life-cycle from suggestion to deployment.
- Developed high quality software inline with customer established requirements.
- Guaranteed code quality, conducting peer reviews from development team members and third party providers.
- Built reusable code and libraries to support future projects and optimize workflows.
- Optimized user experience by ensuring well developed, standard compliant front and back-end code.

Skills

Django, Flask, Laravel, Node.js, Express.js, Flutter, React, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Mongo, AWS, Serveless and Event Driven Architecture.

Education

Bachelor of arts in Mass Communication St. Augustin University

Nov 2017 - Nov 2020 Mwanza, Tanzania

Languages

Swahili: NativeEnglish: Advance